<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<samples>
    <sample id="apix-gpio-sample">
        <name>Digi APIX GPIO Sample</name>
        <description>
Sample application to access and manage GPIO lines using the Digi APIX library.
The application uses a gpio as input (e.g. a user button) and another
one as output (e.g. a user led). The application toggles the output GPIO
whenever an interrupt is generated in the input GPIO.
        </description>
        <path>apix-gpio-example</path>
        <platforms>
            <platform>ccimx6sbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6qpsbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulstarter</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulsbc</platform>
        </platforms>
    </sample>
    <sample id="apix-i2c-sample">
        <name>Digi APIX I2C Sample</name>
        <description>
Sample application to access and manage I2C slaves using the Digi APIX library.
The application writes a page of an external EEPROM memory with random
data and then reads the data back to validate it (tested with 24FC1026).
        </description>
        <path>apix-i2c-example</path>
        <platforms>
            <platform>ccimx6sbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6qpsbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulstarter</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulsbc</platform>
        </platforms>
    </sample>
    <sample id="apix-pwm-sample">
        <name>Digi APIX PWM Sample</name>
        <description>
Sample application to access and manage PWM lines using the Digi APIX library.
The application enables one PWM line of the board using a frequency of 
1000Hz. Then, progressively modifies the duty cycle in a loop from 10% to 
90% and vice-versa.
        </description>
        <path>apix-pwm-example</path>
        <platforms>
            <platform>ccimx6sbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6qpsbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulstarter</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulsbc</platform>
        </platforms>
    </sample>
    <sample id="apix-spi-sample">
        <name>Digi APIX SPI Sample</name>
        <description>
Sample application to access and manage SPI slaves using the Digi APIX library.
The example application writes a page of an external EEPROM memory with random
data and then reads the data back to validate it.
Most of EEPROM memories are compatible with the sample specifying the page size and
the number of address bytes.
        </description>
        <path>apix-spi-example</path>
        <platforms>
            <platform>ccimx6sbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6qpsbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulstarter</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulsbc</platform>
        </platforms>
    </sample>
    <sample id="apix-adc-sample">
        <name>Digi APIX ADC Sample</name>
        <description>
Sample application to access and manage ADC channels using the Digi APIX library. 
The application enables one ADC channel on the board. After that, the application takes periodic samples and prints the raw value and the value in mv.
        </description>
        <path>apix-adc-example</path>
        <platforms>
            <platform>ccimx6sbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6qpsbc</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulstarter</platform>
            <platform>ccimx6ulsbc</platform>
        </platforms>
    </sample>
</samples>
